<project
    name="ratchet"
    brief="Implementation of the double ratchet algorithm."
    namespace="virgil crypto ratchet"
    framework="VSCRatchet"
    prefix="vscr"
    path="../library/ratchet"
    work_path = "generated/ratchet/">

    <version major="0" minor="3" patch="0"/>

    <license>
        Copyright (C) 2015-2019 Virgil Security, Inc.

        All rights reserved.

        Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
        modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
        met:

            (1) Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
            notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.

            (2) Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
            notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in
            the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
            distribution.

            (3) Neither the name of the copyright holder nor the names of its
            contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from
            this software without specific prior written permission.

        THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE AUTHOR ''AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESS OR
        IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
        WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
        DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT,
        INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
        (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
        SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
        HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT,
        STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING
        IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE
        POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

        Lead Maintainer: Virgil Security Inc. &lt;support@virgilsecurity.com&gt;
    </license>

    <require project="common" feature="library"/>
    <require project="foundation" feature="library"/>

    <module name="assert" from="shared"/>
    <module name="library" from="shared"/>
    <module name="memory" from="shared"/>

    <enum name="error"/>
    <enum name="msg type"/>

    <class name="ratchet common"/>
    <class name="ratchet common hidden"/>
    <class name="ratchet key utils"/>
    <class name="error"/>
    <class name="ratchet x3dh"/>
    <class name="ratchet skipped messages"/>
    <class name="ratchet receiver chains"/>
    <class name="ratchet message"/>
    <class name="ratchet cipher"/>
    <class name="ratchet chain key"/>
    <class name="ratchet message key"/>
    <class name="ratchet receiver chain"/>
    <class name="ratchet receiver chain list node"/>
    <class name="ratchet skipped message key"/>
    <class name="ratchet skipped message key list node"/>
    <class name="ratchet sender chain"/>
    <class name="ratchet keys"/>
    <class name="ratchet"/>
    <class name="ratchet session"/>

    <wrapper lang="swift"/>
</project>
